<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA maxImageDimension="480" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" bgColor="0x181818" frameWidth="20" stagePadding="15" thumbnailColumns="5" thumbnailRows="4" navPosition="right" navDirection="LTR" title="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>1.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>A woman runs past burning shacks in Nairobi's Mathare slum during post-election violence. 31 December 2007. Photo: Julius Mwelu/IRIN 
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>2.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>A woman tries to salvage what little is left of her property in Mathare slums, Nairobi, after properties were set ablaze. Kenya, January 2008. Photo: Julius Mwelu/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>3.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>A resident of Mathare slums cries in pain after being tear-gassed, Mathare slums, Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. Post-election violence has been rampant in most parts of the country, forcing many to flee their homesteads. Photo: Julius Mwelu/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>4.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Mathare residents move out of the slums following the post-election skirmishes, Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. Most of the necessities, including water, have become very scarce in the slum. Photo: Julius Mwelu/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>5.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Internally displaced people line up to receive clothes donated by well-wishers, Jamhuri showground, Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. Many Kenyans have been displaced by the post-election violence. Photo: Allan Gichigi/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>6.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>A policeman controls a crowd of internally displaced people queuing up for food aid at the Jamhuri showground, Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. According to the UN, 250,000 people have been displaced in Kenya and 600 killed by violence following the disputed elections. Photo: Allan Gichigi/IRIN

</CAPTION>
</IMAGE><IMAGE>
	<NAME>7.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Internally displaced people queue up for food aid at the Jamhuri showground, Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. According to the UN, 250,000 people have been displaced in Kenya and 600 killed by violence following the country’s disputed elections. Photo: Julius Mwelu/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>8.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Women line up to receive food aid at the Nairobi showground, Kenya. January 2008. The effects of post-election violence in Kenya continue to reverberate throughout the country. An estimated 250,000 people have fled their homes. Photo: Julius Mwelu/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>9.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>A policeman controls internally displaced people queuing up for food aid at the Jamhuri showground, Nairobi, Kenya. January 2008. According to the United Nations, 250,000  people have been displaced in Kenya and 600 killed by violence following the country’s disputed elections. Photo: Allan Gichigi/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>10.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Women and children line up to receive clothes donated by well wishers, Jamhuri grounds, Nairobi, Kenya. Jan 2008. Many Kenyans have been displaced by the post-election violence that rocked Kenya. Photo: Allan Gichigi/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>11.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Some of the internally displaced people receive food aid in Kibera, Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. More than 700,000 people live in 10 “villages”, where sewage channels and a railway cut through corrugated iron and mud-built homes. Photo: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>12.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>A displaced woman gets food for herself and her child at the Nakuru showground, Kenya, January 2008. Many families have been displaced as a result of post-election violence that occurred in Kenya. Photo: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>13.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>An internally displaced child receives food at the Tigoni police station from well-wishers, Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. Photo:Allan Gichigi/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>14.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Internal displaced persons arrive at the Nakuru showground to seek shelter, Kenya, January 2008. An estimated 250,000 people have fled their homes and need food, shelter and essential medicines. Photo: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>15.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Children line up to receive food aid at the Nakuru showground, Kenya, January 2008. Thousands of people have been displaced since the post-election violence that hit Kenya. Photo: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>16.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Children line up to receive food aid at the Nakuru showground, Kenya, January 2008. The effects of post-election violence in Kenya continue to reverberate throughout the country. An estimated 250,000 people have fled their homes. Photo: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>17.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Internally displaced persons receive clothes donated by well-wishers at the Nakuru showground, Kenya, January 2008. Their lack of access to hospitals or proper nutrition has created a fragile health situation. Photo: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>18.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Internally displaced people from Mathare slums shelter in the Moi Air Force grounds in Nairobi, Kenya, January 2008. Agencies and NGOs working in the country estimate that 250,000 people have been made homeless by the violence. Photo: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
</SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA>