<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA maxImageDimension="480" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" bgColor="0x181818" frameWidth="5" stagePadding="15" thumbnailColumns="4" thumbnailRows="2" navPosition="right" navDirection="LTR" title="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>refugee 1.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>South Africa's Lindela repatriation centre, just outside Johannesburg, is the largest detention facility for undocumented migrants in the country. The bulk of the detainees are from Zimbabwe and Mozambique and are economic migrants.  © Antony Kaminju/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>refugee 2.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>A guard takes the chains off one of the new arrivals at Lindela. In theory, 30 days is the maximum period of time a detainee can be held before being deported. An unknown number of migrants manage to evade the police and immigration authorities to stay in the country. © Antony Kaminju/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>refugee 3.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Zimbabwean Innocent Sitore, 18, stands in line to be processed. According to the International Organisation for Migration, 118,000 Zimbabweans were deported from South Africa between January and July 2007 for being in the country illegally; 80,000 were repatriated in the last six months of 2006.  © Antony Kaminju/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>refugee 4.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Zimbabwean Lilian Dube, 22. Despite the threat of arrest and deportation, economic conditions in Zimbabwe drive people to repeatedly come to South Africa to look for work. Around 17 percent of those deported are women. © Antony Kaminju/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>refugee 5.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Naledi Dube, from Zimbabwe, shows her inky hands after her fingerprints were taken. An estimated three million economic migrants - a quarter of the population - have quit Zimbabwe; their remittances are vital to families at home.  © Antony Kaminju/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>refugee 6.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>An immigration officer searches through files at Lindela. There have been repeated allegations of rights abuses, including beatings by guards, poor health services, corruption, and the denial of access to immigration officials. © Antony Kaminju/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>refugee 7.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Whiling away the time. "Deportation is for those who do not have money. Those who can pay police or immigration officers never get [caught]," a detainee told IRIN. The Department of Home Affairs says it has a "zero-tolerance policy" towards corruption.  © Antony Kaminju/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
</SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA>