<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA maxImageDimension="480" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" bgColor="0x181818" frameWidth="5" stagePadding="15" thumbnailColumns="4" thumbnailRows="2" navPosition="right" navDirection="LTR" title="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>01.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Begun in the early 1970s, Aysh Warrwa is still growing and though mains services are now provided to the lower part of the neighbourhood, higher up, residents fend for themselves. Electricity and water are tapped from the mains supply, with small electric pumps used to push water through rubber pipes, which are often suspended house to house alongside electricity cables, 2 April 2007. © Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>02.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>From the top of the mountain, Abu Ali and his family have an unbroken view down on the city for which they left their home on the coast six years ago, but which still does not recognise them as residents, 2 April 2007.© Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>03.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>At the end of a half dug trench in upper Aysh Warrwa, a man watches despondently as a child hops over smelly liquid, raw sewage, which is oozing from the ground, 2 April 2007.© Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>04.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>In 1991 seven children in Aysh Warrwa died from a massive electric shock thought to have been caused when the live current from the electricity cables came into contact with the water piping running just alongside it,2 April 2007.© Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>05.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Nabil Ashraf, deputy Local Administration and Environment (LAE) Minister, is working with the Japanese International Cooperation Agency (JICA) to draw up a ‘Master Plan’ for Damascus that will provide a blue print for land use across the city,2 April 2007.© Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>06.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Further services such as a compact rubbish truck have also recently been provided to residents. Yet many problems remain, 2 April 2007.© Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>07.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Hassan Saqqar Salamah’s house was partially destroyed by the Maraba council on claims the outside steps were built illegal. “How can I be doing anything illegal when the whole area has no legal blueprint?” asked the builder, 2 April 2007.  © Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>08.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Between four to five million people live in Damascus and its surrounding countryside, making it by far the most inhabited region in Syria, 2 April 2007.© Hugh Macleod/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

</SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA>