<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<simpleviewerGallery maxImageWidth="480" maxImageHeight="633" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" frameWidth="5" stagePadding="20" thumbnailColumns="4" thumbnailRows="3" navPosition="right" title="" enableRightClickOpen="true" backgroundImagePath="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-00.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Tens of thousands of child beggars fill the streets of Senegal. The majority of them are talibés, students of religious leaders who are forced to beg for money to sustain their teachers. Currently, many of these children are trafficked from Guinea-Bissau.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-01.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Mamoud Kebé, 13, spent a year in Senegal after his uncle sent him with a marabout, or religious leader, to study the Muslim holy book, the Koran. He has since been returned to Guinea-Bissau, but he is an orphan and his relatives have not yet been found. He lives at a school run by the association SOS-Talibés Children.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-02.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Recruiters travel around the villages of Guinea-Bissau finding children, as young as 4 and as old as 19. They tell parents they will give their children a religious education. Once they have gathered enough children, they come together at a meeting point and travel to the border, where they bribe a guard to let them cross into Senegal.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-03.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Seven people arrested in an alleged trafficking operation sit in a detention centre in Guinea-Bissau. There are no walls or bars; prisoners come and go as they please. A recruiter can make up to 150,000 CFA francs (US$340) by bringing Bissau children to southern Senegal for one month to work the cotton fields during harvest season.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-04.jpg</filename>
	<caption>For months, children at a government-run welcome centre in the Senegalese capital, Dakar, have been preparing to return home. Here is one child's illustration of boarding the plane.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-05.jpg</filename>
	<caption>"Other children leave on their own, walking by foot from the [Senegalese capital] Dakar to Guinea-Bissau. The children are not protected. They are exposed to everything," says Jean Dricot, head of UNICEF in Guinea-Bissau. "They don't all make it. There are many deaths."</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-06.jpg</filename>
	<caption>One parent (far left, in white) waits to take home his son, as staff sort through the files of 18 children who arrived at a transit house in Gabù run by AMIC, a local association involved in the repatriation of children to Guinea-Bissau.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-07.jpg</filename>
	<caption>"I would wake up at 4 a.m.," one talibé explains. "I didn’t have breakfast. I studied the Koran until 6 a.m., went begging until 11 a.m. and then studied for another three hours. At 2.p.m., I begged for my lunch. Then I studied until 6 p.m., played a bit of soccer and, at 7 p.m., went to collect firewood. Then I begged again until 9 p.m., ate and slept."</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-08.jpg</filename>
	<caption>"The trafficking continues," says Laudolino Carlos Medina, of the organisation AMIC. "But now, people are becoming aware of this phenomenon in Guinea-Bissau." The objective of the mixed schools is to convince parents that their children can get a good education without going to Senegal.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-09.jpg</filename>
	<caption>A handful of these students also live at the school, because they have returned from Senegal, but their families have not yet been found. “For a child who is the victim of trafficking at the age of four years old, and doesn’t know where he is from, it is very difficult,” says Jean Dricot, head of UNICEF in Guinea-Bissau.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-10.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Malam Bau Ciro, son of a Koranic teacher, set up the association SOS-Talibés Children in 2001 to help child beggars in Guinea-Bissau. He now runs a mixed Portuguese/Arabic school in Bafatà.</caption>	
</image>
<image>
	<filename>GWSN-11.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Mamdou Kandé, an ethnic Fula from a village near Bafatà, sent his son with a brother-in-law who promised him a religious education for his child, but "it was a lie." His son spent one year in Senegal begging, and has now been reunited with his father.</caption>	
</image>
</simpleviewerGallery>