<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA maxImageDimension="480" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" bgColor="0x181818" frameWidth="5" stagePadding="15" thumbnailColumns="4" thumbnailRows="2" navPosition="right" navDirection="LTR" title="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2180.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>With 800,000 residents in just 7.25sq km, Manshiet Nasser on the edge of Cairo is one of the most densely populated areas in Africa. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2232.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Manshiet Nasser sits on the rocky spurs where Egypt's Eastern Desert Plateau meets the Nile Valley. Residents urgently need more water, sewage and refuse facilities. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2216.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Egypt's urban population is 40 percent larger than it was 10 years ago. 14 percent of the population is under six years of age. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2111.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>New regulations will allow Manshiet Nasser residents to legally own their own houses. The land they stand on is being sold at about LE150 [US $26] per sq m. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2106.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Narrow streets and a lack of amenities mean that rubbish from households accumulates in unhealthy heaps. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2130.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Sewage flows from overhanging buildings destabilise the sandstone. A local girl was killed here by falling rock in 2006. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2219.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Planners and engineers involve local people in the ongoing development process. 80 percent of the workforce for the water and sewage projects must come from Manshiet Nasser. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>DSC_2143.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Cairo Governorate officials want to see the Manshiet Nasser model developed in all the city's informal areas.. 10th May 2007, © Jeff Black /IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>



</SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA>