<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<simpleviewerGallery maxImageWidth="480" maxImageHeight="480" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" frameWidth="5" stagePadding="15" thumbnailColumns="8" thumbnailRows="2" navPosition="left" title="" enableRightClickOpen="true" backgroundImagePath="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<image>
	<filename>01.jpg</filename>
	<caption>The Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation and mental illness in Quinamel, 30km from Guinea-Bissau's capital, Bissau,  February 2008. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption>
	<link>http://www.irinnews.org/IRIN-Africa.aspx</link></image>
<image>
	<filename>02.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Some of the patients at the drug rehabilitation centre  relaxing  in the rehabilitation compound, Desafio Jovem, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau,  February 2008. Of the 70 patients,15 were being treated for crack cocaine addiction while the others were treated for alcohol abuse and mental illness. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>03.jpg</filename>
	<caption>A patient relaxes in the compound at the centre, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau, February 2008. According to Domingos Té, an evangelical pastor who established the centre, the number of drug addicts at Desafio Jovem is just the tip of the iceberg. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>04.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Some of the women at the rehabilitation centre plaiting hair, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau's capital, February 2008. In the three years since this country become a major trans-shipment point for drug traffickers bringing cocaine from South America to Europe, many locals have begun consuming the drug. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>05.jpg</filename>
	<caption>A patient on a bench inside the Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation in Bissau, Guinea-Bissau's capital, February 2008. It is the only facility of drug rehabilitation in the country. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>06.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Patients at the Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau's capital, February 2008. Many addicts are brought to the centre by force when they are aggressive and dangerous. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>07.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Patients sleeping inside the drug rehabilitation centre, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau, February 2008. The consumption of hard drugs in West Africa is underreported, according to Yahya Affinnih, associate professor at the department of African-American studies at John Jay College of Criminal Justice in New York. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>08.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Patients sleeping inside the drug rehabilitation centre, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau, February 2008. “We give them sedatives at first to calm them down but we have almost no resources or trained staff,” said Domingos Té, an evangelical pastor who established Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation and mental illness in Quinamel, near Guinea-Bissau's capital Bissau in 2000. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>09.jpg</filename>
	<caption>A woman taking a rest inside the drug rehabilitation centre, Desafio Jovem, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau's capital, February 2008. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>10.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Patients sleeping inside the drug rehabilitation centre, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau, February 2008. “We never see the vast majority of people taking pedra. Most are hidden away is towns and villages. Often they are said to be processed by bad spirits but the only bad spirit they have is the drug,” said Domingos Té, an evangelical pastor who established Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation and mental illness in Quinamel, near Guinea-Bissau's capital Bissau in 2000. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>11.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Patients receiving a meal Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation and mental illness in Quinamel, near Guinea-Bissau's capital Bissau. The head of the centre, evangelical pastor Domingos Té, said that conditions are basic as he has few resources. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>12.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Patients sharing a meal at the Desafio Jovem drug rehabilitation centre, Bissau, Guinea-Bissau's capital, February 2008. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>13.jpg</filename>
	<caption>"Overcoming the addiction is hard work. All we at this centre can do is provide some discipline and spiritual guidance," says Domingos Té, an evangelical pastor, who set up the centre in 2000. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>14.jpg</filename>
	<caption>"Most of the addicts are men in their early 20s, although we also see many young women addicts," says Domingos Té, an evangelical pastor, who established the centre in 2000.  Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>15.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Not all the patients are being treated for crack cocaine addiction but others there for alcohol addiction and mental illness have also used crack at some time, Domingos Té, an evangelical pastor who established Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation and mental illness in Quinamel, near Guinea-Bissau's capital Bissau in 2000. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
<image>
	<filename>16.jpg</filename>
	<caption>Pedra, as crack cocaine is called locally, is a smoked form of cocaine mixed with water and baking soda (sodium bicarbonate) and then heated. It is cheaper than cocaine powder and also stronger and more addictive, said Domingos Té, an evangelical pastor who established Desafio Jovem centre for drug rehabilitation and mental illness in Quinamel, near Guinea-Bissau's capital Bissau in 2000. Credit: Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</caption></image>
</simpleviewerGallery>