<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA maxImageDimension="480" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" bgColor="0x181818" frameWidth="5" stagePadding="15" thumbnailColumns="10" thumbnailRows="1" navPosition="right" navDirection="LTR" title="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>01.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>The urbanisation of poverty: In the poorest countries of the world, slums make up between 30 percent and 70 percent of the urban population. The hallmark of  rampant urbanisation is the growth of slums – no longer an exception or a pocket of poverty and deprivation within a city. According to some estimates, more than half the world’s poor will live in cities by 2035. Because the locus of world poverty is dramatically shifting from the rural to the urban context, the battle to meet the Millennium Development Goals will be fought in cities more than in the countryside as poverty has, indeed, come to town. © Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>02.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Dhaka, Bangladesh. In addition to being a potential engine of economic prosperity, the city has the capacity to be an efficient means to distribute the maximum welfare to the maximum number of citizens at the lowest cost. According to the State of the World’s Cities 2006/7, “Inequitable distribution of resources and anti-poor policies have led to a rising urban poverty, which impedes the sustainability of cities and impacts their economic viability.” Even in rapidly industrialising ‘miracle growth’ countries such as China and India, urban poverty remains a persistent problem as national GDP rates have risen much faster than national poverty rates have fallen © Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>03.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Dhaka, Bangladesh. Bangladesh is possibly the most disaster-prone country in the world. In any calculation of  human vulnerability or risk, Bangladesh, because of its high-density population, must rank near the top. The natural disasters visited upon it read like a list of Biblical plagues. Worldwide, slum and squatter communities develop in dangerous environments. In claustrophobic urban areas, available space is most often found on cliff sides, flood plains and toxic ground. In many cases natural disasters have already affected these areas and will strike again, which explains the land’s availability. People with few options will settle on a risky flood plain, or in the shadow of a volcano, pesticide factory (as in Bhopal, India) or a liquefied gas facility (as in Mexico City). The urban poor are forced to make what author Mike Davis describes as “a wager against disaster”. In the case of flood-prone Dhaka, the odds are stacked against them.©  Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>04.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Nairobi, Kenya. “Say no to violence” say residents of slums in Nairobi, Kenya, where the largest informal settlements are in the grip of gangs who control the crime and many businesses. The police offer little solace to bullied inhabitants. According to UN-HABITAT’s latest report, over the past five years 60 percent of all urban residents in developing countries have been victims of violence. As a result, there has been rapid growth of the private security industry and of urban gated communities for those who can afford it. However, the urban poor usually have to fend for themselves. © Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>05.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Dhaka, Bangladesh.In Dhaka, the homeless and urban poor sleep as close to their workplaces as possible. The often-illegal, unrecognised, unassisted and under-valued millions of urban poor struggle to fend for themselves, but their large and growing numbers suggest cities neglect them at their peril. By not addressing housing and land-rights issues more practically, cities can only be storing up future problems for themselves and their residents. © Manoocher Deghati / IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>06.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Nairobi, Kenya. Fish on sale in Kibera slum. Nairobi, Kenya, is a city of well-stocked supermarkets, international restaurants and endless street-side stalls of fresh fruit. However, proximity to food does not always mean access to food. With an average income of US $1 to $2 per day, most slum dwellers all over the world focus most of their attention on earning enough money for food and water. Quality of diet is also a problem, as well as hygienic food preparation and storage. © Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>07.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Dhaka, Bangladesh. A woman breaks rocks while cradling her child. The economic imperative of the urban poor means all family members need to be earning income. For women, the burden is magnified by their traditional responsibilities to raise children, produce food and water, maintain the home and care for the sick and elderly. The problem of employment for most urban poor is that it is generally informal, impermanent, small scale and hand-to-mouth in nature. ©  Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>08.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Dhaka, Bangladesh. A woman works at a tannery in Dhaka, Bangladesh. In a city of more than 13 million people, waste water and chemicals from numerous different unregulated businesses drain together with domestic waste, solid waste and rainwater to create a noxious health hazard for the urban poor, who have nowhere else to live but close to, or above, the water. During the perennial flooding of many slum areas of Dhaka, they are forced to live in the contaminated water. © Manoocher Deghati/IRIN
</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>09.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Nairobi, Kenya. An elderly woman in Mathare slum in Nairobi, Kenya. While most urban slums are characterised by an exponentially rising cohort of youth – many of whom are unemployed – the old also struggle to survive their last years in insecure, makeshift housing. Caught in the all-too-common poverty trap of the informal economy, many elderly have little to show for a lifetime of work, having raised families who are also caught in the struggle. © Manoocher Deghati/IRIN </CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>10.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Addis Ababa, Ethiopia. Someone asleep under advertising signs in Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, which is enjoying fast growth and a construction boom while between 60 percent and 80 percent of its residents are said to live in slums. Urban slums are a sharp contrast against symbols of affluence, as economically dominant minorities share city space with those who provide them cheap labour. Studies suggest that as economic globalisation advances, great disparities between the rich and the poor become more apparent.© Manoocher Deghati/IRIN</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
</SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA>