<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA maxImageDimension="480" textColor="0xFFFFFF" frameColor="0x333333" bgColor="0x181818" frameWidth="5" stagePadding="15" thumbnailColumns="4" thumbnailRows="2" navPosition="right" navDirection="LTR" title="" imagePath="" thumbPath="">
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>01.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Cattle markets are functioning again in Borena but many livestock perished during the drought and there are few animals for sale. NGOs that help with restocking programmes try to purchase animals from local markets for redistribution to poor pastoralists.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>02.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Yabello: A Borana woman on market days.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>03.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Livestock markets in Borena are crowded, noisy places. When buyer and seller reach agreement on a price, the two seal the deal by clapping hands togethers.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>04.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Nothing is wasted when animals are slaughtered. Here, Borana women are selling camel fat.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>05.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Animal skins are another importance source of cash income for pastoralists and an area where considerable commercial potential exists if markets can be developed and improved curing techniques introduced.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>06.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>The sale of fresh milk is an important source of cash income for pastoralists as well as being a nutritious food supplement for children. As cattle begin to calve, milk production has increased substantially and today's price on the market is about half of what it was at the beginning of 2001.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

<IMAGE>
	<NAME>07.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>After each successive drought, the number of Borana pastoralists who turn to farming is increasing. NGOs such as CARE and Action for Development support this transition to a more settled way of life through the provision of expert advice, seeds and tools. As people gain experience in working together they often form associations or farmers' cooperatives.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>08.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>There are few plough oxen available in Borena. By necessity, agro-pastoralists sometimes use camels for farm tasks… and are satisfied with their performance.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>09.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Though Borana society is traditionally based on the husbandry of cattle, recently there has been a trend towards keeping more sheep and goats - said to be more resistant to drought and reproduce faster. With good rains, some pastoralists are hoping to recover their herds - and food sufficiency - in one season, others are more skeptical, saying at least two to three years of favourable conditions are needed.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>10.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Community self-help is one of the hallmarks of Borana society. These four young women were part of a group that worked on the rehabilitation of the pond in the background. The workers received a daily wage of 6 Birr (about US $0.80) instead of the usual 8 Birr (US $1) the difference being the voluntary contribution of the community towards the project. Now enlarged by 18,000 cubic metres, the pond contains enough water for the livestock of 40 Ollas (each Olla, or village community, being approximately 200 people) for the 3-4 month duration of the long dry season.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>11.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>With materials and technical assistance provided by CARE, four Ollas came together to volunteer the labour needed to build this cistern storing 100,000 litres of clean water for use during the dry season. The people agreed among themselves to prohibit the use of the land in the catchment area in order to prevent contamination of the water supply.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>12.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Water is life in the rangelands of southern Ethiopia where pastoralists and their animals always have to be within easy reach of both water and pasture. To keep both people and animals alive during time of drought water often has to be carried long distances by road tanker, a difficult and expensive operation. A number of NGOs are working with local communities to improve access to clean water in drought-prone areas of Borena by drilling wells and installing robust hand pumps such as this.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>
<IMAGE>
	<NAME>13.jpg</NAME>
	<CAPTION>Due to the risks involved, the Borana have been discouraged from the traditional seasonal practice of burning the rangeland grass. As a result, more and more grazing is being lost due to bush encroachment. Manual clearing areas such as this is an activity being supported by NGOs through the use of food-for-work.</CAPTION>
</IMAGE>

</SIMPLEVIEWER_DATA>